gogroopie.com 2017-01-16

# GoGroopie Privacy Policy

The Go Groopie website [www.gogroopie.com](http://www.gogroopie.com/) (the “Website”) is owned and operated by Go Groopie Limited, a company incorporated in England & Wales with company number 07363687 and having its registered office at Alpha House, 100 Borough High Street, London SE1 1LB(“we”, “us”, “our”).

This policy statement (the “Policy”) sets out the basis on which any personal data that we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the Policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. Please note that use of the Website by you is subject to the Policy and the Website’s Terms And Conditions of use ("Terms and Conditions"). Where this Policy uses a word starting with a capital letter, that term will be defined in the Terms and Conditions or elsewhere in this Policy. By using this Website, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, in whole or part, you should not use this Website. Please note that this Policy applies only with respect to the information collected on the Website and not any information collected or obtained through other methods or sources.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is Go Groopie Limited. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable data protection laws in the UK).

Our Policy ensures that any information you provide us remains private and secure. To reassure you, below we provide details of the information you provide to us, and how it will and, more importantly, will not be used. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. If you want to check the information that we hold about you or if you have any questions at all about this Policy or Website, please do not hesitate to contact us by email at [support@gogroopie.com](mailto:info@gogroopie.com). If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

1\. Personal Information

We may collect personal information from you in the following manners:

  * Information provided at the time of registering to use the Website and subscribing to the Service (including without limitation email details)
  * Information provided at the time of purchasing Vouchers on the Website. This may include (but not limited to); first and last name, postal address, e-mail address, date of birth and telephone numbers
  * We do not store credit card details
  * Information provided by you by filling other forms on our site; this may include posting materials to the Website or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information if you report a problem with our Website.
  * We may keep a record of any correspondence between yourself and us.
  * We may ask you to complete surveys for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of any transaction you carry out on our Website.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, web blogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

2\. Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and cookies

We may collect information about your computer including; IP addresses, operating system and browser type, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer this Website. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. Your IP address is also used to help identify you during a particular session and to gather broad demographic data. This data may be used to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Similarly, we may obtain information about you via cookies. A cookie is a file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer using the functionality of your browser. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on the Website. Once you close your browser(s), the cookie simply terminates. The information allows us to identify you, improve our site and deliver a better and more personalised service. You may choose to modify your browser to prevent cookie use - but if you do this the Website may not work properly and you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser settings to refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Website. These cookies will enable us to;

  * estimate our audience size and usage patterns
  * track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to the Website
  * store information about your preferences
  * customise our site according to your individual interests
  * speed up your searches
  * recognise you when you return to our site

Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, and you can find more information about these cookies in our 'cookie policy.' One such advertiser is Google. GoGroopie are currently using the following Google Analytics Advertising features:

  * Remarketing with Google Analytics
  * Google Display Network impression reporting
  * DoubleClick platform integrations
  * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting

You can opt out of these Google Analytics Advertising features by following the instructions below. You can also opt out by clicking on the following link <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

_How to delete cookies_

You can delete cookies from your device by using your internet browser. However, please bear in mind that if you delete any cookies, settings previously made on our website will be lost and it may have a negative effect on your browsing experience.

If you choose not to allow cookies then please follow the link below that corresponds to the browser you are using. You will then find detailed information on how to control cookies for your browser. Remember that if you turn off cookies in your browser then these settings apply to all websites, and not just this one:

• Safari: http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html

• Safari (mobile): http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677

• Mozilla Firefox: http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies

• Internet Explorer: http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835

• Internet Explorer (mobile): http://www.microsoft.com/windowsphone/en-us/howto/wp7/web/changing-privacy-and-other-browser-settings.aspx

• Google Chrome: http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=95647

• Blackberries: http://docs.blackberry.com/en/smartphone_users/deliverables/32004/Turn_off_cookies_in_the_browser_60_1072866_11.jsp

• Android: http://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022

• Opera: http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/

• All other browsers: Please look for a ‘help’ function in the browser provider

All personal information is retained in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable data protection laws in the UK. All information you provide to us will be held securely within our systems in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. We hold data up to 3 years after it is last accessed or used by us. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using technologies provided by our secure payment processing providers.

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things,  the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Whilst we take reasonable precautions to safeguard this information, we may be unable to prevent unauthorized access to such information by third parties or inadvertent disclosure of such information during transit. Users acknowledge this risk when communicating with the Website.

We use the information we hold about you to properly provide you with the Service and for marketing ourselves to you. The information allows us to;

  * ensure that our Website content is effectively presented for you and for your computer
  * provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes
  * carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us
  * allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service, when you choose to do so
  * notify you about changes to our Service
  * enable us to comply with our advertisers’ wishes by displaying the Advertisement to a targeted audience

The Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This Policy applies solely to information collected by us on the Website.

Please note that we may email you for the following purposes:

  * as part of the Service. For example, we may send emails to you in the following circumstances:
  * after registration to the Website, notifying you of your account details;
  * reminder emails about the services we offer (particularly if you have not used them yet or not used them for a while);
  * to send you information or Vouchers which you have asked for;
  * as a newsletter;
  * as promotional emails; and
  * to offer related services to you from affiliates companies of Go Groopie Limited.

Please note that these are opt-in email options selected when you register to the Website. However, in terms of any marketing or promotional emails we may send, we will always give you the chance to opt-out (or unsubscribe) from them in the future.

From time to time the Website may request information from you via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. Contact information may be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use of and satisfaction of the Website.

If you choose to use our referral service for informing a friend about the Website, we will ask you for your friend's contact details, including (but not limited to) first and last names and email addresses. We will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The information is discarded after the email is sent.

We are committed to protecting the privacy of the users of our Website. We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Website and it is our policy not to sell or pass any personal information to any other organizations (outside of Go Groopie Limited, our subsidiaries or affiliates) unless we are required to do so for fraud prevention and detection. However, we may pass personal information to our agents, professional advisors and subcontractors to help us with any of our uses of your data set out in this Policy. For example, we may use third parties to provide us with marketing or customer service assistance or send it to a credit card provider to process a payment. **We will never sell or rent your personal information to anyone else for their marketing purposes without your consent.**

We reserve the right to disclose personal information in order to:

  * comply with applicable laws;
  * respond to governmental enquiries (or enquiries from a legal, government or quasi-government or local authority agency or Internet protection agency of any type);
  * comply with a valid legal process or procedure;
  * to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or
  * to protect our rights or property, this Website, and/or other users and subscribers of this Website. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets
  * if we sell all or substantially all of our assets and are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its subscribers will be one of the transferred assets; or
  * if there is any sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganisation or liquidation of Go Groopie Limited.

We also may share aggregated demographic information with our partners, clients and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

Please note that as part of any personal information sharing which we list above, we may send your information internationally including to countries outside the European Economic Area. Some places outside of the EEA may not have adequate data protection laws at all or may offer differing levels of protection of personal information which are not as high as in the UK. By submitting personal information to us, you acknowledge that provided we have used your data in the ways set out in this Policy, we cannot be held responsible for any use of your data by third parties who receive and process your data.

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [support@gogroopie.com](mailto:info@gogroopie.com).

Our site contains links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

For more details about your rights under the Act, the rules we have to adhere to in collecting and store your information and how you can check your data records, please visit **[www.dataprotection.gov.uk](http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/)**

Please note that this Policy forms part of the Terms and Conditions for use of this Website and forms part of the Agreement between you and us. We may, from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or part, at our sole discretion. Any changes to this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised policy on the Website. If we change this Policy then depending on the nature of the change we may announce the change a) on this page, b) on the homepage of the Website or c) by email, if we have your email address, so that you may be constantly aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the Website following any changes will constitute your agreement to any such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or part, you must terminate your use of the Website.

If any information regarding you needs to be corrected, updated or changed it is your responsibility to advise us of the required amendments. If you inform us that you no longer desire our Service, we shall correct, update or remove your personal data provided to us.

After completion of your transaction, your payment details will not be held on our records and are destroyed from our data files immediately.

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [support@gogroopie.com](mailto:info@gogroopie.com).

This Agreement and any dispute arising out of if will be governed by English law. Any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with this Agreement or its formation (including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England and Wales.
